Brooklyn, New York

Sculptor and graphic designer turned developer with an accessibility focus. I have over three years of experience developing websites and digital design for businesses ranging from e-commerce to educational institutions. I take an interdisciplinary approach to interactive media and computer networking technology. My other interests include teaching programming, digital accessibility, and making generative sound objects.

## **Technical Skills**

- Full Stack Web Development React, VueJS, Wordpress, NodeJS + ExpressJS, Flask, Postgresql, Mongodb
- Operations \*NIX System Administration, Git, Heroku, Docker, Squid, Wireshark, cPanel
- Programming Languages Bash, Javascript, Node JS, Python, Go, C
- Digital Accessibility Standards WCAG 2.1, Section 508

## **Professional Experience**

2015- MARK OF THE LAM

Freelance Developer, New York City, Ho Chi Minh City, Los Angeles, Berkeley

- Design and develop websites for business ranging from personal artists to independent publishing houses to promote products, events and services with clients located in Israel, Qatar, Hong Kong, and United States through Upwork.
- Implemented a social media api for a client to automate pulling social media posts for display on website
- · Developed end to end websites for multiple CMS including Wordpress, Wix, Squarespace and GhostCMS
- · Work with clients and account managers to deploy websites to production, to troubleshoot bugs and errors

2018-2020 New York University - ITP

Graduate Assistant - Web Accessibility Developer, New York City

- Developed an accessibility compliant front-end interface for a project database to meet NYU accessibility initiative guidelines in accordance to WCAG standards
- · Created training materials to conduct accessibility audits with assistive tech including VoiceOver, Jaws, and Lighthouse/WAVE
- Mentored and trained students in web accessible programming paradigms so students will consider impact of accessibility throughout their development career

2018–2019 LINCOLN CENTER FOR THE PERFORMING ARTS

Digital Accessibility Fellow, New York City

- · Created accessibility training material for engineering and legal departments to promote access for a diverse customer base
- Audited internal and external digital media of a world-class performing arts institution and write recommendations to meet WCAG 2.1 and Section 508 compliance
- · Prototype a fully compliant digital map of campus accessibility features to simplify wayfinding

2017–2018 Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology & Education

Visiting Lecturer - Introductory Programming, English, Ho Chi Minh City

- Developed an introductory English/programming curriculum in the Clanguage for non-native English speaking engineering students, and worked with student leaders to promote extracurricular English study
- · Led supplemental workshops in specialized programming topics such as web design and portfolio building

## Education

Fall I 2020 Participant

Recurse Center, New York City

May 2020 Interactive Telecommunications, Master of Professional Studies

New York University, New York City

Dec 2015 Media Studies & Art Practice, Bachelor of Arts

University of California, Berkeley, Berkeley

May 2013 Graphic Design, Associate of Arts

College of the Canyons, Valencia